http://www.cleanpower.org/privacy

Privacy Policy
Clean Power Campaignadvocating for policies and programs geared toward sustainable, renewable resourcesHome
About
What is the Clean Power Campaign?
Print
Font Size:
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
When you visit CleanPower.org the following information is collected:
1. The type of the domain from which you accessed the Internet.2. The date and time you accessed CleanPower.org.3. The IP address from which you accessed CleanPower.org.4. The type of browser software used to view CleanPower.org.
When you visit the CleanPower.org website, personally identifying information is not collected, unless you choose to provide such information. Personally identifying information is collected when submitted through one of the following web forms: Contribution, Email Sign-up, Contact Us, Tell A Friend, Volunteer, and Take Action pages.
Submitted information is collected and used for campaign related purposes related to the Clean Power Campaign. We also work closely with Democratic candidates, parties and allied organizations and may share some basic contact information with them, and they may contact you.
Personal and financial information is required when making a contribution to the Clean Power Campaign. This information is used to process your contribution or merchandise request. All contributions made through CleanPower.org are regulated by federal election law.
If you have questions about this privacy statement please feel free to contact us.
Paid for by Clean Power Campaign.
Design by Trilogy
